aminus3.com 2019-03-29

# Aminus3 Privacy Policy

Last updated: 22 May, 2018

**Aminus3 respects your privacy.** This Privacy Policy applies to the Aminus3.com website (“Aminus3”) which includes all subdomains of Aminus3, as well as officially branded Aminus3 applications (apps). This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect on Aminus3 and how we use that information. By using Aminus3, you consent to the terms & conditions of this Privacy Policy.

## What We Collect

Through the usage of Aminus3 you provide Personal Information to us, such as your name, email address, contact details, geographical location, as well as optionally you provide demographic information, such as date of birth, gender, and other preferences. You provide us with Personal Information when you:

  * Create an account and subscribe to any of Aminus3's hosted services (“Services”)
  * Participate in a survey, contest, or challenge on Aminus3
  * Contact us by email, such as to request assistance with the Services, or to provide us with your comments/feedback
  * Purchase a product from Aminus3 such as photographic prints or other media
  * Post personal information in connection with your photos (example, in a photo description or comment) or in other forums or interactive areas on Aminus3

We may collect information such as your IP address, the type of computer or browser you use, and the pages on Aminus3 that you have visited. We may also collect information regarding the referring sites to Aminus3. Your Personal Information may be linked to your Anonymous Information.

We do not intend that children will use Aminus3 without permission from a parent or guardian. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 16 years of age, nor will we accept registration from them without parental consent.

When you sign up for an account on Aminus3 you are asked to enter your real name. This information is not displayed or shared to the public. Your identity (or "display name") on Aminus3 is determined solely by you.

### Cookies

In order to provide a consistent experience on Aminus3, we use browser "cookies" to track your identity as a member of Aminus3. A cookie is a small file that is transferred to your computer from Aminus3 that contains information related to your account. The main purpose of the cookie is to allow you to browse Aminus3 without entering your email and password repeatedly. In a similar way, cookies are used to retain information when you post a comment as a convenience to avoid having to enter the same information the next time.

Some third parties may place cookies or web beacons on Aminus3 to track traffic or advertisement data. This recording of data is done anonymously and is not linked to, and does not track, any personally identifiable information about users of Aminus3.

You are free to delete or block cookies from Aminus3 at any time however, some basic site functions may not work as expected.

Aminus3 uses Google Analytics to help us optimize our user experience. There are several ways to opt-out of Google Analytics through the use of a browser plugin or other security solution. More information on this can be found on [Google's website](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Google Analytics data may be retained for a period of up to 25 months. 

## How We Use the Information We Collect

We use your Personal Information that you provide to validate that you are a legitimate user, to communicate with you, to customize content for you, and to conduct research with the aim of improving Aminus3.

We use information that is not personally identifiable to determine how people use Aminus3. For example, this data gives us information about how often users click on advertisements, which images are viewed most frequently, and which areas of Aminus3 are the most popular.

## How Long Do We Keep Your Data?

As described in the Aminus3 [Terms of Service](https://www.aminus3.com/terms/#section-license), Content shared on Aminus3 including photos, comments, and your account information will remain on the Aminus3 Servers as long as your account is active. Once you remove your account or request to remove data, it can take up to 30 days before data is fully removed.

As a public photography website, it is possible that Content may be shared from Aminus3 to other third-party websites such as social media communities. Please be aware that even after your Content is removed from Aminus3, it is not always possible to remove Content shared in this manner.

## Where is Your Data?

Aminus3 servers are located in the United States and all data shared with Aminus3 will be stored in the United States

## How We Share Your Personal Information

Aminus3 does not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in the limited circumstances described in this Privacy Policy. We may share personal information with third party vendors who assist us in performing internal functions necessary to operate our business. These functions may include, for example, analyzing traffic information or other data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card transactions, and fulfilling or delivering orders. In all cases we limit the information shared with our third party vendors to that which is necessary to carry out those functions.

We will disclose personal information when required by law (example, a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order) or by the request of law enforcement authorities; to initiate, render, bill and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our customers' rights, property or safety; to protect our customers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of Aminus3. If we become part of another organization, including without limitation, by merger, change of control, sale of assets, or other acquisition, the acquiring organization will obtain and have access to the Personal Information collected by Aminus3 and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may share aggregated Anonymous Information with third parties, business partners or affiliates. Such information does not identify you individually.

## Links to External Sites

Aminus3 may contain links to other websites on the Internet. Links to these other sites or content are provided for convenience only and we have no control over the content, privacy or security of such third party sites. Any personal information you provide on these external websites is subject to that third party's privacy policy and terms of service.

We encourage you to learn about the privacy and security policies of of any third party sites you use before providing them with personal information.

## Security

We make a best effort to secure your data through the use of industry standard practices, tools, policies, and by encrypting via Secure Socket Layers (SSL) nearly all traffic to and from the Aminus3 server.

As no system is ever 100% secure, please be advised that there is a possibility your information may be disclosed or accessed by the accidental or unauthorized acts of others.

All financial transactions involving credit card data are handled by third-party payment processing vendors. Aminus3 does not store or have access to your credit card information. Please review our third party vendor’s privacy policy for more details: [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/be/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) and [Stripe](https://stripe.com/privacy/)

When you create an account on Aminus3, you are asked to create a password. It is your responsibility to use a secure password and to ensure the confidentiality of this information. Aminus3 will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email.

You are responsible for your conduct on Aminus3 and any activity that occurs on your account. If you believe your account has been compromised and may have been used for malicious intent, or if you have any concerns about your account security, please [Contact Us](https://www.aminus3.com/contact/).

## European Data Protection / GDPR

Sections of this privacy policy have been updated to ensure compliance with the European General Data Protection Regulation (EU/2016/679).

This includes a clearer explanation of what data we collect, how long we keep that data, how you can opt out of data collection, and how to contact us for more information.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our services change and expand. We will notify you of these changes by posting the modified Privacy Policy on Aminus3 and indicating the last date the Privacy Policy was updated (at the top of the page). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to see if it has been updated and to ensure you understand how your information will be used.

## Further Information

If you have further questions or concerns specifically in regard to the Aminus3 Privacy Policy, please email privacy@aminus3.com.
